[
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Yoda's home?",
      "answer1": "Naboo",
      "answer2": "Kashyyk",
      "answer3": "Dagobah",
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "C-3P0 is fluent in how many languages?",
      "answer1": "3",
      "answer2": "2 milion",
      "answer3": "Over 60 million languages",
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who built C-3P0?",
      "answer1": "Anakin Skywalker",
      "answer2": "Boba Fett",
      "answer3": "Princes Leia",
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How old is Yoda when he dies?",
      "answer1": "69",
      "answer2": "900",
      "answer3": "232",
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the young Jedi Knight who becomes Darth Vader?",
      "answer1": "Luke Skywalker",
      "answer2": "Anakin Skywalker",
      "answer3": "Obi Wan Kenobi",
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the ‘Rule of 2’?",
      "answer1": "There can only be 2 Sith Lords at one time.",
      "answer2": "Eye for an eye",
      "answer3": "Brunch and dinner",
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who stars as the famous Han Solo in the original Star Wars films?",
      "answer1": "Brad Pitt",
      "answer2": "Harrison Ford",
      "answer3": "Daniel Radcliffe",
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Luke and Leia’s mother?",
      "answer1": "Padmé Amidala",
      "answer2": "Ahsoka Tano",
      "answer3": "Jyn Erso",
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": " What age did Padmé Amidala become a queen?",
      "answer1": "9",
      "answer2": "14",
      "answer3": "18",
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who tried to save Han Solo by disguising and infiltrating Jabba’s palace?",
      "answer1": "Master Yoda",
      "answer2": "Princess Leia",
      "answer3": "Chewbacca",
      "correct": 2
    }
  ]